Smith, Edwin S. Papers 5549
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV. Additional Papers 1932-1971
  - Sub-Series B. Subject Files
    - Poland Business Proposals., 1945-1947 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Correspondence re Polish trade, etc. with M.D. Deutsch, Ambassador Oscar N. Lang, "Proposal for the Organization of Trade Between Central Europe and Latin America"; report to R.B. Roger of Rogers International Corp. re Polish Assignment, re Development of polish Business.
    - Putney School., 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Calendar of events; newspaper clippings; correspondence with school's director Carmelita Hinton re teaching, re Putney School Faculty Association, re teachers' strike and negotiations, re resignation; personal correspondence re resignation; routine.
    - Southampton College Library for Black History., 1968-1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Newspaper clippings; correspondence with Mrs. Martin Luther King, Jr. re Martin Luther King, Jr. Collection; correspondence to Harry Belafonte; pamphlets; speech by Smith re collection; routine.
    - United Public Workers (Teachers' Division)., 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Correspondence with Senator Claude Pepper from UPW Vice President Roy Eldean re Smith's appointment to Panama Canal Zone and denial of visa; correspondence re visa application and probe; correspondence re suspension of New York Teachers; "Jim Crow Discrimination Against U.S. Employees in the Canal Zone."
  - Sub-Series C. Miscellaneous
    - Revised Drafts of History of Labor. (Box 11, Folder 17-21)
      Includes reference notes re ICGTU, CISL, ERP, AFL-CIO conventions, UAW, miscellaneous.
    - Miscellaneous Publications. Includes: NLRB "Written Trade Agreements in Collective Bargaining"; International Labor Conference Record of Proceedings 1933., 1933-1962 (Box 11, Folder 22-25)